market4free.com 2012-12-30

# 

_Sharing and Disclosure of Personal Information._ Except as described below, Market4free.com will not willfully disclose, share, sell or rent your personal information to any individual or business entity outside of Market4free.com. In an effort to serve you better and improve your online experience while using the Web and/or Market4free.com Services, we may disclose your personal information in a responsible manner in the following circumstances: 

  * We have your consent.   
  * We may provide personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We may also provide such information to our service providers who help with our business operations.  
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, court orders, subpoenas, other legal process, or enforceable governmental request, or otherwise comply with law; (b) enforce our Terms of Use, or investigate any potential violations thereof; (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect the rights, property or safety of Market4free.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

In the event that Market4free.com is sold, has its assets acquired or transferred, whether voluntarily or involuntarily, or merges or becomes affiliated with any other division, individual or entity, any user information owned or under the control of Market4free.com may be one of the transferred assets. In this event, we will notify you before any personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

_Sharing of Non-Personal Information._ We may share with some of our business partners or third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information. Such information does not allow them to identify you individually in any way.

_(a) Security and Protection._ Your personal information is stored on our servers housed and maintained in secure locations. We treat data as an asset that must be protected. For that reason, we take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data using a wide range of tools, systems and procedures including, without limitation encryption (using Secure Socket Layer-SSL), passwords, multiple checkpoints, firewall protection, employee training and screening and physical security. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our Web and/or Market4free.com Services. You transmit all such information at your own and sole risk. Therefore, although we make our best efforts to ensure security and protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect that your personal information will always remain private.

_(b) Protection of User Account._ Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose or share your password to anyone. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving the Web to protect access to your information from subsequent users. Remember, that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify us and change your password.
